(Leonard:)-Where's Penny?
-She returned to her apartment.
(Sheldon:)I presume to shower and vomit.
(Sheldon:)Not necessarily in that order.
(Leonard:)Wonder why she didn't say goodbye.
(Sheldon:)Are you expecting me to offer
an explanation of human behavior?
I know. I thought as an outsider...
(Leonard:)...you might be able to provide
a fresh perspective.
Well, I have no difficulty
believing you are not butter.
(Leonard:)-Oh, hey.
-Oh, hi.
(Penny:)-I gotta run. Early shift.
-Okay, I'll walk down with you.
(Leonard:)So last night was fun, huh?
PENNY: Yeah, it must've been.
I just threw up in my closet.
LEONARD:
Bummer.
(Leonard:)I was thinking tonight
maybe we could catch a movie.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, tonight's not great for me.
(Leonard:)Doesn't have to be tonight.
I'm free pretty much always.
(Penny:)Leonard, last night was a mistake.
When you say "mistake,"
do you mean a fortunate mistake...
(Leonard:)...like the discovery of penicillin?